Office of Physical Planning Records, 1869-1994 (bulk 1946-1994): Finding Aid AC154
University Archives
- Series 1: Building Project Records, 1879-2002 July 2; 91 boxes
  - Dickinson Hall Renovation - Budget, 1966; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - East Pyne Building - Movable Equipment, 1966; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Requisitions/Purchase Orders/Invoices, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Receipts, 1966 June-1967 July; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Office Supplies and Equipment, 1963-1967; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Pyne Administration - Title I Grant, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Telephone Contacts, 1963-1967; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Plasma Physics, 1964-1969; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Frick - Purchase Orders, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Aaron Burr, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Engineering Quad, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Von Neumann, Change of Use, 1976-1980; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Von Neumann, 1974-1978; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - New South, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Moffett, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Guyot Hall, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Murray-Dodge, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - T. Smith House, 1975; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Maclean House, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - 10 Mercer Street, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Firestone Library, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Firestone Library - Minutes, Budget, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Firestone Library - Correspondence, 1972-1977; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Prospect, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Law School Study, 1975; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Wilcox Hall, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Biochemical - Community, 1977-1980; 1 folder (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Revised Blackbooks, 1968-1975; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Toilet Facilities - Co-Ed, 1970; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Facilities Usage - Room/Class Weekly Schedule, circa 1970; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Office of the Dean of the Faculty - Course Plan, circa 1970; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Budget Estimate - Plumbing, 1970; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Extra Building Layout, 1970; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Occupancy Data, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - College and University Facilities Survey, 1958-1960; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - 185 Nassau Street, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Safety, 1974-1977; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Zoning, 1970; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Landmark Ordinance, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Alexander Renovation, 1979; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Passive Solar Commercial Buildings Design Assistance and Demonstration - Program Opportunity Notice, 1979 July 16; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Zoning, 1955-1974; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Environmental Design Review Application, 1972-1979; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Energy Research Laboratory, 1980; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Energy Research Laboratory - Request for Change Order, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Area Computations G-M, 1965; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Area Computations O-W, 1965; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Area Computations A-F, 1965; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Zoning Ordinance, 1967 November 1; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Architects'/Landscapers' Profiles, Brochures, 1964-1976; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Inventory of Physical Facilities and Human Resources, 1951 February 15; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Purchase Requisitions, 1965; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Departmental Abbreviations, 1967; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Room Occupancy List, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Room Allocation and Occupancy Listings, 1966; 1 folder (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Policy and Standards, 1968-1973; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Macmillan Suite and Moran, 1973; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1972-1975; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Institutional Space Inventory Techniques II, circa 1967; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Data Processing, 1975; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Prospect Street Clubs, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Club Data, circa 1970; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Hlafter - Clubs, 1974; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Toilet Facilities - Co-Ed, General Budget, 1970; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Program Codes, Correspondence, Etc, 1965-1971; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Completed List, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Inventory Correspondence, 1974; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Space Inventory - Special Features, 1971-1973; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Inventory Correspondence, 1974; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Computer Time, 1968-1976; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - State of New Jersey Survey, circa 1970; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - J. P. Moran Transfer Case, circa 1965; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Classrooms and Office Surveys, 1964-1976; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Computer Access Information, 1974; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Data Processing Instructions, 1969-1974; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Background Information, 1974; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Biochemical Building - Furniture, 1978-1979; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Guyot Hall - Constantine-Paton Alterations, 1954-1978; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Dormitories - Miscellaneous, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Firestone Library - Princetoniana, 1976; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Grounds - Miscellaneous, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - McCosh Infirmary, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - McCosh Counselling Purchase Orders, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Ground - Firestone Plaza, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Palmer Hall, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Nassau Hall, 1975-1978; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Delaware and Raritan Canal Basin Park, 1973-1976; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Firestone, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - New South, 1976; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Green, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Graduate College, 1976-1978; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Vivarium, 1976; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Space Utilization Study, 1976 April 9; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Interoffice Correspondence, 1976; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Moffett, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Feasibility Study - Occupational Health and Safety Labs, 1976 April 27; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Grounds, 1976-1980; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Palmer Stadium, 1975-1979; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Music Building, 1959-1965; 1 box
    - Furnishings, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Conference Reports, 1960-1965; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Moore and Hutchins - Agreement Payments, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Professor Mendel, 1959-1964; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Progress Photographs, 1962-1964; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Progress Schedule, 1963; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Mr. Moran, 1962-1963; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Mr. Orr, 1963; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Review of Plans and Specifications, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Suppliers, 1962-1963; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Subcontractors, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Transmittal Notices, 1960-1963; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Music Building, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Moore and Hutchins - General Correspondence, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Gift Opportunities, circa 1964; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Keys, 1963; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Change Orders, 1962-1964; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Mr. J. B. C. Moore, 1960-1964; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Preliminary Estimates, Budget, Areas, Specifications, Etc, 1959-1963; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Construction Schedule, 1963; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Music Auditorium, 1957-1964; 1 box
    - Moore and Hutchins - Agreement Payments, 1959-1964; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Preliminary Estimates, Budget, Program Requirements, Etc, 1958; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence - Mr. Orr, 1957-1962; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Conference Reports, 1958; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - General Correspondence, 1957-1961; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Turner Construction Company Payments, 1962-1964; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Sander and Constant, 1980-1983; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Moffett, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Moffett Lab Alterations, 1982-1983; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Palmer Stadium, 1979; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Palmer Stadium, 1982; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Commons, circa 1970; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Models of Dorms, 1979-1981; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Residential Life, 1975-1983; 1 box
    - Study I - Haskins and Sells, Co-Education, 1975; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Study II, 1978; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Study III, 1979 April-1981 May; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Residential Life, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Commons, 1978-1983; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Memos, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Minutes, 1980 March-December; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Summary of Transition Materials, 1981 July 24; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Talks, 1980; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Residential Life, 1977-1980; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Schematic Design - Rockefeller and Mathey Colleges, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Butler Budget, Etc, 1980; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Butler, 1980; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Dormitory Data, 1966-1978; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Work Sheets - Dorm Study, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Dorm Use Chart, 1970; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Student Housing, 1971-1976; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Moffett, 1977-1983; 1 box
    - Budget, 1978-1981; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Moffett, 1981-1983; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Progress Photographs, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Modernization Lab, 1980-1983; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Modernization Lab, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Modernization, 1978-1981; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Renovations, 1977-1982; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Modernization, 1979; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Moffett, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Minutes and Proposals, 1978-1982; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Book #4, 1980 April; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Book #5, 1980 November; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Moffett, 1981; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Renovations, 1982; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Sander and Constant, 1978-1980; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Undergraduate Housing, 1969 October 31; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Student Housing, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Roy Perlmutter: "Contemporary Design of Student Facilities", 1971 May 14; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Renovation Feasibility Study - Witherspoon Hall, 1970 January 15; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate Housing Review, 1969 October 31; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Educational Facilities Laboratories Report - Student Housing, 1972; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Princeton Dormitory Study, 1977 September; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Dorm Study, 1977; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Energy Research Laboratory, 1976-1981; 2 boxes
    - Furniture, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Architectural Selection, 1977; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Architectural Selection, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Progress Photographs, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1977 March; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1977 January; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1976 December; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Municipality, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Minutes, 1977-1979; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1977 May; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1977 October; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1977 June; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1979 November; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Budget Contracts, 1977-1980; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - H & H and Sert Jackson, 1977-1978; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Transmittals, 1977-1980; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Energy Research Laboratory, Miscellaneous I, 1977-1981; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Toilet Room Surveys and Proposals, 1969-1973; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Shipping Tickets, 1969-1973; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Student Facility Planning, 1968; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Student Facility Planning, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Consultants, 1970-1975; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Elm Club - Interiors, 1970; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Elm Club - Miscellaneous, 1970; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Elm Club, 1967-1970; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Furniture, 1970; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item List - Furniture, 1969; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Office Expenses, 1970; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - East Pyne Language Laboratory, 1970-1973; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Auditory Research Laboratory, 1970; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Frick 102, 1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Accounting, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Furniture, 1967-1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Office Expenses, 1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - I. M. Pei and Partners, 1971-1974; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Research Laboratory for Related Chemistry, 1961-1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Peyton Hall, 1967-1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Food Services - Purchase Orders, 1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Dean's House, 1966-1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - 133 Dickinson, 1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - T. Smith House, 1970-1974; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Elm Club - Air Conditioning, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Elm Club - Furniture Inventory, circa 1970; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Elm Club, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Chancellor Green, 1973-1975; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Madison Hall - Housing Office, 1972; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Stanford, 1972; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Rowing Tank Final Payment, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Accounting, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Commencement, 1972; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Financial Data - Spelman Dorms, 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Bowers, Lewis C. and Sons, 1972-1975; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Post Office, 1972-1975; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Request for Computer Production, 1970-1973; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) - Guggenheim Laboratory, 1972; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Memorials, 1969-1972; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Peyton Hall - Library, 1972; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Harvard, 1965-1968; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Students Housing, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Capital Planning, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Women's Housing, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Student Facility Planning, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Furniture, 1972-1976; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Invoices/Purchase Orders, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Physics, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Stanhope Hall, 1970-1974; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Brown Hall, 1970-1972; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Holder Hall Alterations, 1970; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Dodge-Osborn - Purchase Orders, 1970; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Wilson College (7012), 1970; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - 1938/1939 Halls - Purchase Orders, 1970; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Brown Hall - Purchase Orders, 1970; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Palmer Laboratory, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Eno Hall - Purchase Orders, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Elm Club - Purchase Orders, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Whig Hall - University, 1970-1974; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - 1979 Hall, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Procter Hall - Basement, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Reunion Hall, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - 91 Prospect, 1964-1966; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Sports Pavilion, 1964-1966; 2 folders (Box 31, Folder 5-6)
  - Sports Pavilion, Tower Construction - Payment Agreement, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Sports Pavilion, Eldredge Snyder - Payment Contract, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Sports Pavilion, Athletic Facilities - Correspondence, 1964-1966; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Stanhope Hall, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Princeton University Store - Specifications, 1967 July 15; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Tennis Pavilion, 1961; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Tennis Pavilion - Matthews Construction, Payment Agreements, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Tennis Pavilion, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - West College, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Whig Hall, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - West College, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Taylor Room, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Moffett, 1970; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Wilcox Hall, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Wilcox Hall, 1970-1973; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Green Hall, 1970; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Princeton Inn (7104), 1971; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Palmer Hall - Oriental Languages, 1967-1971; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - New South, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Gauss Hall - Purchase Orders, 1971; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Frick Chemistry Lab, 1970; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Frick Lab, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - 70 Washington Road - Purchase Orders, 1970; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - 70 Washington Road, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - University Site Study, 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Pei Plan Site Study, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Nassau Hall - Renovations, 1967-1970; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Public Relations, 1958-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Campus Mail System, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Shelter Designs - For Protection against Radioactive Fallout, 1960 February 1; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Fallout Shelter Program, 1959-1963; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - John Kennedy, 1964-1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Academic Space Assignments, 1964 June; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Invoices, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Purchase Orders and Requisitions, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - University League Nursery School, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Budget - East Pyne, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Wyman House, 1958-1960; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - McCosh Alterations, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - 5 Ivy Lane, 1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Palmer Square Incorporated, 1963-1965; 1 box
    - Correspondence, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Office Building, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Job Meeting Minutes, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Progress, 1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Grounds and Buildings Department Building (A-1220), 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Service Buildings, 1959-1965; 1 box
    - Service Buildings, 1960-1962; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Addition - General Correspondence, 1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Addition, 1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Matthews Construction Company, Payment Agreements, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Service Buildings, 1959-1961; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Addition, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Princeton Rendering, 1963 March 13; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Grounds and Buildings, 1961-1963; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Grounds: New Church Courts, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Southwest Area - Parking, 1963; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Parking - Vivarium, 1963; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Parking - Roper Lane, 1963; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Prospect - Alterations Inventory, 1955-1959; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Melanie Kahane Purchase Orders, 1958; 1 box
    - Melanie Kahane Purchase Orders, 1958 January; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Melanie Kahane Purchase Orders, 1958 February; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Melanie Kahane Purchase Orders, 1958 March; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Melanie Kahane Purchase Orders, 1958 April; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Melanie Kahane Purchase Orders, 1958 May; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Melanie Kahane Purchase Orders, 1958 June; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - 1958July, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Melanie Kahane Purchase Orders, 1958 September; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Melanie Kahane Purchase Orders, 1958 October; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Melanie Kahane Purchase Orders, 1958 November-December; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Whig Hall - Contractor, Etc, 1971-1974; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Whig Hall - Consultants, 1970-1973; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Whig Hall - Purchase Orders, 1970-1975; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Greenhouse, 1971; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - West College, 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Guyot - Biology Library, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Guyot - Biology Library, 1970-1972; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Shop Drawings - Guyot Hall, 1971; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Architecture Building, 1967-1970; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Green Hall - Purchase Orders, 1968-1971; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Frick 133 (7030), 1971-1973; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Green Annex, 1970; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Green Annex, 1967-1970; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Green Hall, 1970-1972; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - 171 Broadmead, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Green Hall - Dr. Erickson, 1970; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Laughlin Hall, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Hall, 1879-1970; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - 1879 Hall - Tower Room, 1968-1973; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Clio - Career Services, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Taylor Collection, 1971; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Green Hall, 1970; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Green Hall Annex Alterations - Payments, 1970; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Green Hall Annex Alterations - Payments, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Guyot, 1970; 3 folders (Box 33, Folder 25-27)
  - Student Housing Cooperative Project, 1969-1972; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Inactive File (Miscellaneous), 1968-1972; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Princeton Inn Parking, 1971; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Maclean House, 1970-1973; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Dickinson Hall, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Green Hall - Purchase Orders, 1970; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 33)